

Personal

Name David Messner

Address

Frundsberstraße 13 39049 Sterzing

Phone number +39 328 485 3653

Email

david.messner@protonmail.com

Date of birth

18-05-2001

Gender

Male

Nationality

Italy

Driving license

B, AM

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/david-messner-89b690296

Languages

German Native
English Fluent
Italian Intermediate

David Messner

Robust experience in creating games while working both in a team and individually. Achieves intended concepts according to project requirements by utilizing diverse technology resources. Poised and committed in listening carefully to critiques and requests, incorporating feedback and boosting project outcomes to surpass expectations.

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Science Gaming

FH Salzburg Salzburg, Salzburg

Aug 2022 - Present

Aug 2017 - Jun 2021

This major focuses on the development of computer games and info/ edutainment applications. Game theory, economic and legal aspects of games, modelling, asset preparation, game architecture, game authoring systems, game engines and graphic libraries, game AL, multiplayer games, generative modelling, internationalisation and computer vision as well as augmented reality are part of the studies. Field of study Multi-Media-Technology with focus on Game Development & Mixed Reality

Matura (Equivalent to High School Diploma in Italy)

Technologische Fachoberschule (TFO), Bruneck

Focus on chemistry, materials and biotechnology.

Work experience

Frontend Web Developer

Leitner, Sterzing

Aug 2024 - Dec 2024

Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

uring my internship at Leitner AG as a Frontend Web Developer, I worked on a ski lift control interface using C++ and the MudBlazor component library. My main task was to translate detailed design mockups into responsive and functional user interfaces. I implemented the necessary frontend logic and occasionally used JavaScript to support specific interactive features.

Machine Operator

Milchhof Sterzing, Sterzing

Safely operated machining equipment as part of a collaborative team of operators. I played a hands-on role in equipment setup and adjustment, ensuring optimal configurations for daily operations. Loading raw materials into machines and efficiently unloading finished products were key tasks that I executed with precision to uphold a smooth manufacturing process.

Skills

C#	
C++	
Phyton	
Unity	
Godot	
SFML for C++/C#	
Unreal Engine	
Gamemaker	
Linux	